newhiphopmedia.com 2013-04-03

# Privacy Policy - NewHipHopMedia.com

Privacy Policy  
FreshAsFrankie.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site:

Information Automatically Logged  
We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site.

Cookies  
Our Site uses cookies to make sure you don’t see the same ad repeatedly, and, if you are a member, to keep you logged in.

Advertisers  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here.

Third Party Cookies  
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser.

Contests  
We run contests on our site in which we ask visitors for contact information (like email address). Contact information from the contests is used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary.

External Links  
This site contains links to other sites. FreshAsFrankie.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

Public Forums  
This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

Data Quality/Access  
This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided: You can send email to freshasfrankie@gmail.com.

Contacting the Web Site  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact email freshasfrankie@gmail.com.
